var questions = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: "What is the result of 'C R A B'.split(' ')?",
        a: "crab",
        b: "CRAB",
        c: "['C', 'R', 'A', 'B']",
        d: "['c', 'r', 'a', 'b']",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which line of code adds the attribute 'display: none' to a div?",
        a: "document.querySelector('div').addAttribute('display', 'none')",
        b: "document.querySelector('div').setAttribute('display: none')",
        c: "document.querySelector('div').addAttribute('display: none')",
        d: "document.querySelector('div').setAttribute('display', 'none')",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Which of the following methods joins all elements of an array into a string?",
        a: "Array.prototype.concat()",
        b: "Array.prototype.join()",
        c: "Array.prototype.map()",
        d: "Array.prototype.splice()",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which of the following choices demonstrates the correct syntax of a for loop?",
        a: "for (i=0; i<array.length; i++)",
        b: "for (i=0, i<array.length, i++)",
        c: "for (i=0; i=array.length; i++)",
        d: "for (i=0; i<array.length; i+1)",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a valid String method?",
        a: "String.length",
        b: "String.replace()",
        c: "String.reverse()",
        d: "String.toUpperCase()",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Write the following phrase as an if condition: 'if color is not red...'",
        a: "if (color NOT== 'red')",
        b: "if (color ! 'red')",
        c: "if (color == !('red'))",
        d: "if (color !== 'red')",
        correct: "d"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which line of code adds an event listener that triggers when an element is clicked?",
        a: "elem.addEventListener('clicked', function)",
        b: "elem.addEventListener('click', function)",
        c: "elem.addEventTrigger('clicked', function)",
        d: "elem.addEventTrigger('click', function)",
        correct: "b"
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Which line of code selects a div with an id of 'password'?",
        a: "document.querySelector('#password')",
        b: "document.querySelector('password')",
        c: "document.querySelector('.password')",
        d: "document.querySelector(':password')",
        correct: "a"
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which of the following choices demonstrates the correct syntax for writing a function?",
        a: "function(params) ( )",
        b: "function(params) [ ]",
        c: "function(params) { }",
        d: "function[params] ( )",
        correct: "c"
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "In an object with multiple keys, the keys need to be separated by...",
        a: "semicolons (;)",
        b: "dashes (-)",
        c: "periods (.)",
        d: "commas (,)",
        correct: "d"
    }
];
